Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Photo Materials
  - Prints - The Bowery Concert, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 160)
  - Contact Sheets - Love of a Poet, Battery Maritime Building, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 161)
  - Prints - Love of a Poet, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 162)
  - Negatives - Carbon Monoxide is a Lethal Gas, citywide, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 163)
  - Contact Sheet - Carbon Monoxide is a Lethal Gas, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 164)
  - Prints - Carbon Monoxide is a Lethal Gas, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - Prints - Day Without Art: Electric Blanket, The Cooper Union, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - Negative - Visualize This, citywide, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - Print - Visualize This, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Negatives - Angels Have Been Sent to Me, citywide, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Contact Sheets - Angels Have Been Sent to Me, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - Prints - Angels Have Been Sent to Me, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - Contact Sheets - Black Works, The Kitchen, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - Prints - Black Works, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - Negatives - Not Just the Parade…, citywide, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 174)
  - Prints - Not Just the Parade…, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - Negatives - The Most Exciting Women in Music, citywide, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 176)
  - Contact Sheets - The Most Exciting Women in Music, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 177)
  - Prints - The Most Exciting Women in Music, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - Contact Sheets - The Honeymoon Project, World Financial Center Winter Garden, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - Prints - The Honeymoon Project, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 180)
  - Contact Sheets - Suz/o/Suz, Kaufman Astoria Studios, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 181)
  - Prints - Suz/o/Suz, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 182)
  - Contact Sheet - Memories of New York Chinatown, 70 Mulberry Street, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 183)
  - Prints - Memories of New York Chinatown, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 184)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 8, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 185)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 8, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 186)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 8, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 187)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage: Sounds in the Anchorage, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 188)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage: Sounds in the Anchorage, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 189)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage: Sounds in the Anchorage, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 190)
  - Contact Sheets - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors: Skin, 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 191)
  - Prints - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors: Skin, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 192)
  - Prints - Wigstock, Union Square Park, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 193)
  - Negatives - Masterpieces Without the Director, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 194)
  - Contact Sheet - Masterpieces Without the Director, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 195)
  - Prints - Masterpieces Without the Director, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 196)
  - Contact Sheets - As a Dream That Vanishes…, Guggenheim Museum, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 197)
  - Prints - As a Dream That Vanishes…, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 198)
  - Prints - Fear of Disclosure Project: (In)visible Women, citywide, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 199)
  - Contact Sheets - Our Voices:Our Songs, 208 West 13th Street, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 200)
  - Prints - Our Voices:Our Songs, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - Prints - ["Hybrid Special," CT Benefit auction item], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Negatives - Domestic Violence Milk Carton Project, CT, MD, NJ, NY, PA, DE, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 203)
  - Contact Sheet - Domestic Violence Milk Carton Project, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 204)
  - Prints - Domestic Violence Milk Carton Project, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 205)
  - Print - Use Mass Transit 1, citywide (via billboard), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 206)
  - Print - Roy Cohn/Jack Smith, 33 Wooster Street, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 207)
  - Contact Sheets - Private/Public, citywide, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 208)
  - Prints - Private/Public, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 209)
  - Negatives - Transitions, Inc., citywide, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - Contact Sheets - Transitions, Inc., 1992 (Box 19, Folder 211)
  - Prints - Transitions, Inc., 1992 (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Contact Sheets - Sacrificial Ornament, Municipal Art Society, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Prints - Sacrificial Ornament, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Prints - Fear of Disclosure Project: Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien, citywide, 52 West 8th Street, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 9, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 9, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Contact Sheets - A Surreal Soap Opera, 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Prints - A Surreal Soap Opera, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Contact Sheet - Accountability?, NYC, Chicago, Los Angeles, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Prints - Accountability?, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 221)
  - Contact Sheets - Two Spirits Speak Out, Grand Central Terminal, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Prints - Two Spirits Speak Out, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Contact Sheets - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program…, citywide (via television), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Prints - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program…, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Negatives - Use Mass Transit 2, citywide (via billboard), 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Contact Sheets - Use Mass Transit 2, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Print - Use Mass Transit 2, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Contact Sheet - Higher Ground, 268 Mulberry Street, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Prints - Higher Ground, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Negatives - Victory Music Series, New Victory Theater, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Contact Sheets - Victory Music Series, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Prints - Victory Music Series, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Negatives - Hairy Tales, citywide, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Contact Sheets - Hairy Tales, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Print - Hairy Tales, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 236)
  - Negatives - Art in the Anchorage 10, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 10, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 238)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 10, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 239)
  - Negatives - In Honor of Allen R. Schindler, citywide, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 240)
  - Print - In Honor of Allen R. Schindler, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Negatives - 42nd Street Art Project, 42nd Street between 7th and 8th Avenues, 1993, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - Contact Sheets - 42nd Street Art Project, 1993, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Prints - 42nd Street Art Project, 1993, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Negatives - Universal Family Album, 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Contact Sheets - Universal Family Album, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 246)
  - Prints - Universal Family Album, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Prints - Dyke TV: Weekly Art Segment, citywide (via television), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - Negatives - Underdevelopment in Progress/500 Years, Soho 20 Gallery, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Contact Sheets - Underdevelopment in Progress/500 Years, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Print - Underdevelopment in Progress/500 Years, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - Contact Sheets - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program…, citywide (via television), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Prints - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program…, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 253)
  - Contact Sheets - Body Politics, Great Hall, The Cooper Union, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 254)
  - Prints - Body Politics, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 255)
  - Contact Sheets - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress, 45 Greene Street, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 256)
  - Prints - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 257)
  - Contact Sheets - Art in the Anchorage 11, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 258)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 11, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 259)
  - Contact Sheets - Creative Time's 20h Anniversary Celebration, Apollo Theater, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - Prints - Creative Time's 20th Anniversary Celebration, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 261)
  - Contact Sheets - 1st Annual Sara D. Roosevelt Park Summer Festival, Sara D. Roosevelt Park, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - Prints - 1st Annual Sara D. Roosevelt Park Summer Festival, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Contact Sheets - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors: Wild Style, 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - Print - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors: Wild Style, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - Contact Sheets - Combat Zone: Campaign HQ Against Domestic Violence, 110 Mercer Street, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 266)
  - Prints - Combat Zone: Campaign HQ Against Domestic Violence, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Prints - alternative art space photographs, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Negatives - Fear of Disclosure Project: Out in Silence and Not a Simple Story, citywide, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Contact Sheet - Fear of Disclosure Project: Out in Silence and Not a Simple Story, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Prints - Fear of Disclosure Project: Out in Silence and Not a Simple Story, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 271)
  - Negative - Poster Campaign, citywide, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 272)
  - Prints - Art in the Anchorage 12, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 273)
  - Prints - Medicinal Garden, outside Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 274)
  - Print - Rent-a-Body, citywide, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 275)
  - Negative - Art in the Anchorage 16, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 276)
  - Negative - Leap, 2 Columbus Circle, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 277)
  - Negatives - Tibor in Orbit, Times Square and citywide [via milk cartons], 2000 (Box 19, Folder 278)
  - Negative - 59th Minute: Portrait, Times Square, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 279)
  - Negatives - DNAid Deli Cups, citywide, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 280)
  - Negatives - Tribute in Light, World Financial Center, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 281)
  - Prints - Holiday Light Show, Grand Central, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 282)
  - Prints - Art on the Plaza 3: Peace, The Ritz-Carlton, 2 West Street, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 283)
  - Negatives - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, Undated (Box 19, Folder 284)
  - Negatives - one unidentified strip of negatives, Undated (Box 19, Folder 285)
- Series V: Video and Film
  This series contains the videotaped material from the Creative Time Archive. Titles are arranged chronologically by year. Compilation tapes are arranged chronologically by first year represented on tape. Material includes performances, news broadcasts, source material, artist samples, and other miscellaneous recordings. There is a small amount of film material.
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    - Big Apple Minute, Ruckus Manhattan [Press], 1976 (Case 179.0312)
      General note
      Format: DVD-R
      Duration: 00:02:00
      Original Format: 3/4" video cassette
    - Art on the Beach (aerial videotaping by Joe Kos), 1978 (Case 179.0324)
      Duration: 00:14:00
    - Art on the Beach (video by Joe Kos), 1978 (Case 179.0278)
      Duration: 00:16:00
    - "Creative Time Art on the Beach" 1978 Aerial Videotaping by Joe Kos, ID: 179.0717 (Case 179.0717)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements Note
      Format: DVD
      Duration: 00:07:00
    - Art on the Beach, 1978; ID: 179.0699 (Case 179.0699)
      Duration: 00:18:00
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], TV Spots, 6/86, 6/81, 9/89, 11/83 [Press], 1981, 1983, 1986, 1989 (Case 179.0557)
      Duration: 00:37:00
      Original Format: VHS
    - Big Apple Minutes, Art on the Beach, Centenary, 1982; ID: 179.0690 (Case 179.0690)
    - Alice Farley, "The Water Garden" - Cooper-Hewitt Museum, 8/82, 1982 (Case 179.0238)
      Duration: 00:21:00
    - "The Water Garden" by Alice Farley, 1982; ID: 179.0687 (Case 179.0687)
      Duration: 00:23:00
    - Art on the Beach - Danny McCusker, "Art in the Anchorage with Warhol", "Big Apple Minutes", 1982 (Case 179.0240)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Drunken Madness", 1983 (Case 179.0242)
      Duration: 00:15:00
    - Station House Opera "Drunken Madness", 1983; ID: 179.0693 (Case 179.0693)
    - Art on the Beach - Live at 5, 5/13/83 [Press], 1983 (Case 179.0477)
      Duration: 00:36:00
    - Art on the Beach '84 MTV Tape, 1984; ID: 179.0747 (Case 179.0747)
      Duration: 00:05:00
    - Creative Time Art on the Beach Highlights, 1984; ID: 179.0705 (Case 179.0705)
    - Art on the Beach - 1984 highlights (Dan Freel, edited master 2/8/85) (Case 179.0413)
    - Art on the Beach (highlight reel), 1984 (Case 179.0316)
      Duration: 00:13:00
      Original Format: 3/4" video cassette,
    - Art in the Anchorage - "The Memory Theater of Giulio Camillo", 1985 (Case 179.0204)
      Duration: [1]--01:04:00 [2]--01:09:00
    - Art on the Beach - Yoshiko Chuma, Lenny Pickett, Fred Wilson, 1985 (Case 179.0322)
    - "Art on the Beach 85 Chuma Dicket Wilson" by Dieter Froese, 1985; ID: 179.0714 (Case 179.0714)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 2), [1985] (Case 179.0332)
      Duration: 00:20:00
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 3), [1985] (Case 179.0320)
      Duration: 00:09:00
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 7), [1985] (Case 179.0318)
      Duration: 00:22:00
    - Art on the Beach - Yoshiko Chuma, "School of Hard Knocks", [1985] (Case 179.0314)
    - Art on the Beach (CBC Master #1), 1985 (Case 179.0326)
    - Art on the Beach (CBC Master #2), 1985 (Case 179.0328)
      Duration: 00:29:00
    - Master #1 CBC Art on the Beach 9/4/85, 1985; ID: 179.0720 (Case 179.0720)
      Duration: 00:17:00
    - Camera Master #2 CBC Art on the Beach (Performance), 1985; ID: 179.0723 (Case 179.0723)
      Duration: 00:19:00
    - Subway Art Live from Underground 2, 1985; ID: 179.0750 (Case 179.0750)
    - Subway Art Live from Underground 3, 1985; ID: 179.0753 (Case 179.0753)
    - Subway Art Live from Underground 4, 1985; ID: 179.0756 (Case 179.0756)
    - Subway Art Live from Underground 5, 1985; ID: 179.0759 (Case 179.0759)
    - Subway Art Live from Underground 7, 1985; ID: 179.0762 (Case 179.0762)
    - Subway Art 8, 1985; ID: 179.0765 (Case 179.0765)
    - Subway Art 9, 1985; ID: 179.0768 (Case 179.0768)
    - Subway Art 10, 1985; ID: 179.0771 (Case 179.0771)
    - Survival Research Laboratories (Mark Pauline, Matt Heckert, Eric Werner), "The Virtues of Negative Fascination", [1985-1986] (Case 179.0599)
      Duration: 01:17:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - John Kelly, 6/22/87, 1987 (Case 179.0501)
      Duration: 00:59:00
    - Art on the Beach (opening) - Mark Antrobus, "Mud People", 1987 (Case 179.0254)
      Duration: 00:25:00
    - Gretchen Langheld, Creative Time Benefit, 6/30/87, 1987 (Case 179.0403)
      Duration: 00:55:00
    - John Torreano, Creative Time Benefit, 6/10/87, 1987 (Case 179.0469)
      Duration: 01:13:00
    - Performance in the Park - Clarice Marshall, 1987 (Case 179.0290)
      Duration: 01:33:00
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], CNN, 8/13/87 (Filmed at Stanford Conference on Design, July 1987) [Press] (Case 179.0597)
      Duration: 00:03:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Contraband, Evol, 1988 (Case 179.0148)
      Original Format: VHS,
    - Art in the Anchorage - Scott Sherk, Joel Sanders, Ed Tomney, Brigid Kennedy, 1988 (Case 179.0210)
      Duration: 01:06:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera (long shot from front), 1988 (Case 179.0208)
      Duration: 01:04:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY", 1988 (Case 179.0196)
      Duration: 01:05:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY" (complete performance), 1988 (Case 179.0212)
      Duration: 01:09:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY" (NTSC Dub), 1988 (Case 179.0214)
      Duration: 01:03:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/14/88 (ledge, stage left, cut-aways), 1988 (Case 179.0405)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/16/88 (3rd row, tight in), 1988 (Case 179.0407)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/18/88 (3rd Row Wide Shot), 1988 (Case 179.0152)
    - Marcos Kurtycz, "Organikwars" 12/8/88-12/10/88; "Organrites" 12/8/88; "One Dos Tres O!" 12/9/88; "Clavarte" 12/10/88, 1988 (Case 179.0459)
      Duration: 01:47:00
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], Shea Stadium 5/19/88; CBS News 5/17/88 [Press] (Case 179.0465)
      Duration: 00:08:00
    - Survival Research [Laboratories], [1988] (Case 179.0603)
    - Survival Research Laboratories, [1988] (Case 179.0553)
      Duration: 01:00:00
    - Tony Fisher, Steven Ausbury, "The Lost Opera", 1988 (Case 179.0463)
      Duration: 00:06:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH" 1990, "Pleasure Life" 1988, 1988, 1990 (Case 179.0541)
      Duration: 00:58:00
    - Merry Conway, Noni Pratt, "As a Dream That Vanishes" 1991; "In the Eye of the Beholder" 1988, 1988, 1991 (Case 179.0461)
      Duration: 01:30:00
    - "Desire Borne", 1989 (Case 179.0382)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Jessie Jane Lewis, "Blind Ally", 6/22/89, 1989 (Case 179.0178)
    - Leni Schwendinger, "Light Site-ings", 11/1/89, 1989 (Case 179.0266)
    - Mark Pauline, 1989 Sculpture Grant Award Exhibition, San Francisco Artspace, July 11-Aug 19, 1989 (Dir. Jonathan Reiss and Leslie Asako Gladsjo) (Case 179.0601)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Karen Finley, "3 Parables and 2 Testimonies", 9/28/90, 1990 (Case 179.0192)
      Duration: 00:40:00
    - HIV TV, Swarthmore College, 12/16/90, 1990 (Case 179.0521)
      Duration: 00:44:00
    - John Kelly, "Love of a Poet", 10/19/90 (Case 179.0437)
    - Kit-Yin Snyder, Enrico IV Set/Installation - Creative Media Conc., 9/25/90, 1990 (Case 179.0435)
    - The Bowery Concert, 9/15/90 (4 PM show), 1990 (Case 179.0417)
    - "Clean Needles Save Lives", [1991] (Case 179.0527)
    - "Needle Exchange" (without credits), [1991] (Case 179.0529)
      Duration: 00:31:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH", Kyoto Municipal Museum of the Arts, Institute Contemporary Arts, Nagoya, Spring 1991 (Case 179.0537)
      Duration: 01:10:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991] (Case 179.0539)
      Duration: 01:01:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991] (Case 179.0543)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Ellen Spiro, Marina Alvarez, "(In)Visible Women", [1991] (Case 179.0445)
      Duration: 00:27:00
    - Jordi Torrent, "Honeymoon", 1991 (Case 179.0439)
    - Antoni Miraldi, "Honeymoon Project" (cued for 10 minute viewing segment, parts I and II), [1991] (Case 179.0142)
    - La Fura Dels Baus, "Suz/O/Suz", 4/1/91, 1991 (Case 179.0186)
    - "Transitions Inc.", 5/9/92, 1992 (Case 179.0441)
      Duration: 00:41:00
    - Fear of Disclosure - Marlon Riggs, "Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien", 1992 (Case 179.0447)
      Duration: 00:48:00
    - Jordi Torrent, "Monuments in Love", 1992 (Case 179.0140)
      Duration: 00:30:00
    - "Patina Du Prey's Memorial Dress", Hunter Reynolds, ICA Boston, 1993 (Case 179.0511)
      Duration: 00:28:00
    - 42nd Street Art Project - Interviews, 1993 (Case 179.0487)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - News All Evening NY 1 6/21/93; News All Morning NY 1 7/30/93; Good Day NY 7/6/93; Daybreak CNN 7/10/93; Channel 9 News 8/2/93; MTV News 8/11/93; NY Views 8/14/93 [Press], 1993 (Case 179.0473)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993 (Case 179.0398)
      Duration: 00:34:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Dyke TV, Episode 19, 1993 (Case 179.0505)
      Duration: 00:45:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Ringside, "Kid Action", 1993 (Case 179.0244)
      Duration: 00:12:00
    - Debra Levine, "Hairy Tales", [1993] (Case 179.0443)
    - Dyke TV Arts Compilation, 1993 (Case 179.0509)
    - Dyke TV, Episodes 1 and 3, 1993 (Case 179.0507)
    - Glenn Belverio, "Two Spirits Speak Out", 1993 (Case 179.0264)
    - Nelson Rodriguez, "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #2), "13 Years" (Draft #3), "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #4), 1993 (Case 179.0519)
      Duration: 00:24:00
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Heaven Earth and Hell", 1993 (Case 179.0366)
    - Creative Time: 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, 1994; ID: 179.0738 (Case 179.0738)
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994 (Case 179.0358)
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994 (Case 179.0431)
    - Creative Time 20th Anniversary Celebration, 1994; ID: 179.0741 (Case 179.0741)
      Duration: 00:50:00
    - Creative Time 20th Anniversary Celebration The Apollo Theater July 7, 1994 (tape 2 of 2), ID: 179.0744 (Case 179.0744)
      Duration: 00:42:00
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration (tape 1), 1994 (Case 179.0392)
      Original Format: HI 8
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration (tape 2), 1994 (Case 179.0394)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 1 of 2), 1994 (Case 179.0609)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 2 of 2), 1994 (Case 179.0364)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 3), 1994 (Case 179.0396)
    - Anniversary Party Interviews, [1994] (Case 179.0485)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - PBS Video, MacNeil Lehrer News Hour, 9/23/94 [Press], 1994 (Case 179.0475)
    - Dyke TV, Best of Winter '94, 1994 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0517)
      Duration: 00:51:00
    - Martha Wilson, Joyce Scott, Blondell Cummings, Reno, Carnival Knowledge, "Body Politics", 2/14/94, 1994 (Case 179.0513)
      Duration: 01:36:00
    - Martha Wilson, Mary Ellen Strom, Peggy Pettitt, Holly Hughes, "Body Politics", 2/15/94, 1994 (Case 179.0384)
      Duration: 01:26:00
    - Rebecca Bollinger, "Alphabetically Sorted", 1994 (Case 179.0202)
    - Use Mass Transit - Hey Bozo! TV Coverage [Press], [1994] (Case 179.0252)
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Vintage: Families of Value" documentary, 1995 (Case 179.0256)
      Duration: 00:01:00
    - VAPP 1995 Application - Gretchen Bender, "Still/Here", "Total Recall"; Ron Kuivila, "VR on $5/Day; Frank Mann, "A Timely Existence"; Grahame Weinbren: "Sonata", "The Erl King" (Case 179.0262)
    - Art in the Anchorage - EAR, Harmony Rockets, 1996 (Case 179.0216)
    - Music in the Anchorage (demo reel), 1996 (Case 179.0156)
    - Paco Cao, "Rent A Body", Carol and Marylyn TV Talk Show, [1996] (Case 179.0467)
      Duration: 00:35:00
    - Pierrick Sorin, "A Very Full Life", et. al., [1996] (Case 179.0158)
    - Adrianne Wortzel, "Technoseduction Exhibition", "My Robotic", "The Ship's Detective" projection installation, [1997] (Case 179.0160)
    - Ange Leccia, "Sabatina", 1997 (Case 179.0411)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage - Rough Footage, 9/11/97, 1997 (Case 179.0170)
    - Magali Claude, "Tiems. Toi droit", "Les Gestes du Travail", "La Chora. Les rumours", 1997 (Case 179.0491)
    - "ATM Art" (5/98), "Gesture as Value" (6/98), BBC [Press], 1998 (Case 179.0304)
    - Ange Leccia, "ISA", 1998 (Case 179.0380)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Detroit Techno, 1998 (Case 179.0162)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Standard and Poor, "Big Night Out", 6/18/98, 1998 (Case 179.0168)
    - Jerelyn Hanrahan, "Gesture as Value", [1998] (Case 179.0306)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, 11/2/98, 1998 (Case 179.0390)
      Original Format: Beta
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial, 11/2/98, 1998 (Case 179.0409)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, [1998] (Case 179.0388)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Installation Video (dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998] (Case 179.0531)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History", BBC, Fall 1998 (Case 179.0533)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History" (installation version, dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998] (Case 179.0535)
      Duration: 00:43:00
    - The Art Guys with Todd Oldham, "Suits: The Clothes Make the Man", 11/2/98, 1998 (Case 179.0573)
    - The Art Guys, [1998] (Case 179.0579)